<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="locale">en</string>
    <string name="home_title">Strategic UX UI designer</string>
    <string name="home_subtitle">I'm a UX/UI Designer with over three years of experience building accessible and
        high-performance digital products. My goal is to create intuitive experiences that truly resonate with people.
    </string>
    <string name="featured_projects_title">Featured\nProjects</string>
    <string name="featured_projects_description">From beautiful websites and intuitive mobile apps to impactful
        user-driven
        projects.
    </string>
    <string name="view_all_projects">View all projects</string>
    <string name="expertise_title">Expertise</string>
    <string name="expertise_description">My design approach is flexible and iterative, adapting to each project's unique
        needs. I handle the entire design process, from UX research and strategy to UI design and prototyping.
    </string>
    <string name="services_website_title">Website</string>
    <string name="services_website_description">Whether you need a more engaging and user-friendly website or want to
        increase its accessibility, I’ll make sure to bring your idea to life.
    </string>
    <string name="services_website_img_description">A mouse icon representing the website service.</string>
    <string name="services_product_title">Product</string>
    <string name="services_product_description">Building scalable and intuitive interfaces, where creativity and
        strategic thinking can help you overcome your biggest design challenge.
    </string>
    <string name="services_product_img_description">A building block icon representing the product service.</string>
    <string name="services_mobile_title">Mobile</string>
    <string name="services_mobile_description">Seamless and intuitive mobile experiences designed to meet users’
        needs.
    </string>
    <string name="services_mobile_img_description">An android icon representing the mobile service.</string>
    <string name="home_big_statement">Creative thinking is the key to solving complex problems.</string>
    <string name="footer_contact_call_out_line_1">Have a project in mind?</string>
    <string name="footer_contact_call_out_line_2">Let's talk!</string>
    <string name="footer_contact_drop_me_message">Drop me a message at:</string>
    <string name="footer_credits">Designed by Amanda, coded by Rafael with love</string>
    <string name="projects">Projects</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>

    <!--  About page  -->
    <string name="about_welcome">Hi, I’m Amanda</string>
    <string name="about_me_paragraph_1">
        I’m a UX/UI designer who creates meaningful digital experiences by blending analytical thinking with visual
        storytelling. My expertise spans the entire product lifecycle, from strategic design and user interface
        development to implementing production-ready products. I’m also passionate about micro-interactions and digital
        accessibility (WCAG), ensuring every solution is comprehensive and user-friendly.
    </string>
    <string name="about_me_paragraph_2">
        I leverage design best practices to drive strategic thinking and make informed decisions that elevate every
        project. My goal is to create intuitive, accessible, and impactful digital experiences that not only resonate
        with users but also meet business objectives.
    </string>
    <string name="about_image_description">Amanda Bicalho profile drawing</string>
    <string name="about_my_journey">My design journey</string>
    <string name="about_my_journey_paragraph_1">
        My journey into design was anything but linear. I’ve always been driven by curiosity, whether it was exploring
        colors with crayons as a kid or diving into the structured world of engineering. It was this unique blend of
        creativity and logic that ultimately led me to UX/UI design.
    </string>
    <string name="about_my_journey_paragraph_2">
        My passion truly ignited during a moment of self-discovery, starting with graphic design and building a strong
        foundation in visual aesthetics. This soon evolved into a deep love for digital design—my true calling. Today,
        I'm proud of the unique path that shaped my approach to design and allows me to see challenges from multiple
        perspectives.
    </string>
    <string name="about_work_experience">Work Experience</string>
    <string name="about_view_resume">View resume</string>

    <!--  Showcase page  -->
    <string name="showcase_project_info_team">Team</string>
    <string name="showcase_project_info_client">Client</string>
    <string name="showcase_project_info_year_duration">Year/duration</string>
    <string name="showcase_project_info_project_type">Project type</string>
    <string name="showcase_project_info_industry">Industry</string>
    <string name="showcase_project_background">Background</string>
</resources>
